<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>REPOSSESSED - Development Log</title>
        <link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html</link>
        <description>Development Log for there upcoming Immersiv Sim REPOSSESSED.</description>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.01.31 - Parts of Level 3 done, music progresses greate, more artworks</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=41</link>
			<description>The first areas of level 3 are done, the environment is mostly completed and configured and assets are all places or already have placeholders. The soundtrack comes along great and so the art. I already started working on two other areas, after those are done work on the side stuff like random location off the beaten path and the final area of Level 3 can start. The starting area is already full finished and filled with triggers and polished to be fully playable and even NPC's and diagonals are already placed there. Play-testing already revealed a few small bugs here and there that I fixed almost immediately. Now the strongest focus is put on finishing Level 3, adding the dialog's and finishing story details for it and then start work on level 4 and 5. I also updated many small thing to improved the general look and feel and also updated the lighting and shadows a bit to be even more high-contrast, have more distance and generally look a bit better.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2026.01.25 - FULL controller support, stable game build, all frameworks done</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=40</link>
			<description>My vacation is over and a lot of game-dev happened too. I started adding the Keybind menu and it escalated more and more until I added FULL controller support with automatic switching of UI and icons (thanks to the great "Controller Icons"-plugin much of it was done much faster then reinventing the wheel (This plugin should become part of Godot IMO.)), added vibrations customized in fell, duration and length for all actions, fully finished the main menu, its code and assets and fixed a lot of bugs. After that I finally finished the last few open ends in the module system and cybernetics API. The current game build is very very stable and now go's into playtesting. While playtester have fun I will continue working on Level 3. Almost everything needed now is just building the levels 3 to 5, writing the dialogs for them, fixing bugs found by playtesters and working with the other artists on the OST and artworks. The only UI still in the oven is the "Cybernetics" menu which is accessed in game. It has most of the "reality breaking"-aspects. I decided to finish and enable that mechanic as soon as the playtester deem the game "tested"-stable xD. Because, as the caption in the trailer already mentions, it allows "reality breaking" levels of scaling of  the game-mechanics and that needs a lot of testing to prevent soft-locks and make it work with the game flow and to be balanced. The Artworks and OST also came along extremely well. A little bit of the OST can be heard in a recent post I made :D.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.12.10 - Level 3 progress and Car</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=39</link>
			<description>Good progress is made. The base code and technical specification are done. Level 3 will use a slightly adjusted Heightmap system. It is used for the base terrain around the main area. Most of the base Heightmap is already done and now needs textures and the assets to be placed. Locations and architectures are also planed out and now need block-out and models to be created. While doing this I had the idea of making the car(s) more then already part of the gameplay loop. How much integration they will get is not fully mapped out yet but they are now drivable and have many fun features (Bellow are screenshots of the drivable version of the car in Level 1. Screenshot 03 and 04 show an extremely early untextured part of Level 3). The soundtrack by static.grl is also making great progress.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.12.04 - A LOT OF GREAT NEWS - LEVEL 2 DONE, Level 1 fixed, work on Level 3 started, A LOT of polish and artist found for the Soundtrack!</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=38</link>
			<description>What has been done: Level 2 just has been fully completed, Level 1 rework and cleanup has been also finished, I fixed many bugs, polished A LOT OF STUFF and optimized HEAVILY. Thanks to this the game is now very stable, looks polished in almost all places, runs a really really great amount faster and plays very well. What comes next: I will now start with Level 3 (the concept, plans and base is done, just needs to be executed now into a playable level). In parallel, Level 2 gets more play-tested from playtester and the dialog's checked/cleaned up, the Augmentation system and the keybinding system gets a fronted and a few back-end things get tight together. One extremely great news is that I got into contact with static.grl and she will make the soundtrack for the game! More about this in future updates/Dev-logs. Also: The creation and publication of the store pages also went well and were receive positively.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.11.25 - Store Pages and Trailer online!</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=37</link>
			<description>It was around 2/3 of a month of work but now all Store Pages are online, the Trailer is public and the Website updated. You won't believe how much you have to do to launch a full Trailer and 2 Store entry's. Now that this is done I will continue fixing bugs that came up in play-testing and trailer production (thankfully nothing big, just a few small things to improve! :D), then do the last few dialog's in level 2 and fix the level 1 environment. And while doing all that also start collecting footage and plan out the last details for level 3 and 4. Level 5 is still in early development. But now more importantly, Wishlist RE//POSSESSED on Steam, itch.io and/or watch the Trailer. Trailer and Links are on the Main page and Links are also directly under here:</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.11.09 - Trailer production started fully, Level 2 mostly done, Level 1 fixed</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=36</link>
			<description>The assets are now far enough to fully start trailer production. A few dialog's and small things here and there are still needed but nothing big at all for Level 2. Level 2 is now done and holy f*ck was that a lot of work. I LOVE THE RESULT! Level 1 is also fixed, but I notices some design issues with it (mainly the environment-visuals and backgrounds) that need a little bit of a visual overhaul here and there after finishing Level 2 Dialog's. After the trailer is public, the SteamPage is live, the mentioned points fixed and Christmas holidays is over, the level 3 development can fully start. The concept already is planed and just needs to be realized.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.10.31 - Gov building done, many new modules added and bugs fixed and path finished</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=35</link>
			<description>The progress is very great considering the circumstances. Why?: I got really sick last week a could not do much until today, but regardless that the GOV building is finished! I also added a lot of finishing touches in many places and added many new modules, Bug fixes too but that is to be expected. Now the only thing between me, the StorePages for wishlisting and the Trailer is the Final FRP building for Level 2 and some more fixing of Level 1. My own deadline of early December considering the holidays at the company's behind the Stores and the approval process AND the video production itself, it could get really tight but I am sure I will get the page and trailer public before new year (at least I hope so). And as written in the past the amount of screenshots with spoilers will go down more and more. Also: The artist I am working with made a few concepts for the game's "cover" and they look great!</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.10.20 - Settings done, working with an artist, last outpost done, work on GOV and FRP building started, fixes needed for level 1 outlined</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=34</link>
			<description>A lot has happen, I had vacation, then fully finished the settings (except for the keybinds, there I still need read and export code to make it available in the UI, will be done later) for the Trailer. The main goal for me was to be able to set graphics and simulation settings and be able to optimize the heck out of the framework so the trailer can represent the reality of how it will run on different hardware. I also wanted to be able to crank the settings to MAX for a little LITTLE bit nicer screenshots :D. After that was done and working I added a little screenshot script so making screenshots much easier. The main reason for doing that script was I finally found an artist to work on the Store Page artworks and Icons (More about them at a later point)! Until now I used KDE's screenshot tool but now that it is in game I can make them much easier and faster. I also finished the last outpost, added many small fixes to bugs I found, extended some existing functionality to be able to have cameras and alarms work with other nodes intertwined. Now two thing that changes about the release: I don't have a date because game dev take so much time, but can say the game will release 2026, maybe early to mid. 2027. I know, gigantic time window but I do what I want with my hobby dream project. About the demo? There will not be one. The time it takes to build levels is better invested into the actual game and I don't want to release one of the current levels as a demo so there will be no demo. But the one thing that tipped me over the edge to that decision was the current Steam Next Fest... . The ABSOLUTE state the selection of games are in is disheartening to say the lest. MANY great demos made with passion, heart and so much talent that definitely made me want the game behind it and wishlist them, but so SO much sh*t made with trash generating machines (I wont write the two letters, f*ck that). I refuse to fight for exposure against that stuff for just a demo (Valve fixed a lot of the trash by now as I just looked again, still dose not change my stands, I will not make a demo and go for a full release). Back to the trailer: It is in pre-production, the scenes and ideas and structure is already planed out, the first few scenes recorded and prepared, but I still need to finish level 2 and fix level 1 a little before I am happy to record it all, cut it and release the trailer, not to mention I need to write the Store Pages too still. Or in short: I will have to hall a*s if I want to release the trailer and Store Pages this year. And also: No I still have not found an artist for the OST. Seems like I will do it myself if nothing changes about that. Only the trailer music is not form me at the moment.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.09.30 - More Updates about performance and Settings</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=33</link>
			<description>As it usually is, you make a Dev-Log, find more things to fix and then improve stuff even more but already wrote about it. Well I will do it anyway. The settings are nearly done. I still need to add some accessibility options like post processing and screen-shake options and adding the presets to automatically apply settings for different kind of PCs and hardware. Keybinding-stuff is also done in the back-end and only needs a UI to interact and change it. I will do that later this year. For development and play-testing a config file change is better anyway. Performance wise I also made huge progress ~again~. In the last Dev-Log I wrote about changing the bullet system, well now I made it multithreaded too. Thanks to a little workaround I was able to make the physics calls from an other thread and so moved over the hole bullet system to it. Now the game really embraces multithreading. Culling, bullets, physics and so on, all handled separately. As you might expect this also need slightly newer hardware but that was also the intention from the beginning to target "slightly" newer hardware. The Forward+ Renderer of Godot needs good Vulkan 1.2 and newer support and that means hardware from 2012~2013/14 onward ideally, so, using Forward+ limits developers already to """newer""" hardware. Aka. as long as the hardware is at least as fast as a SteamDeck it will work very good. The FPS numbers, accordingly, got a GOOD amount even better. Now the SteamDeck can run the game very well and any thing stronger then the SteamDeck runs very, very good. Now with so much freed up CPU space the graphics settings can really push the GPU. I will start working on the last things for Level 2 the next few days, then after that, play-testing and finaly cleaning up Level 1 will be on the agenda and then the Trailer production can start, maybe a little of other levels will make an appearance in it too, may be not.</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.09.26 - Work goes one well. Option menu nearly done and a LOT of performance optimizations</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=32</link>
			<description>Work goes on extremely great. I made huge progress with the different parts of the Level 2 World. Only one house still needs to be filled with its decorations and one dialog and the GOV and FRP building can be start to be worked on. But I was not only busy with that (obviously since the last log is nearly 20 days ago), I tested hardware on all PCs I have and then heavily optimizing the game. A few examples are: The core of the bullet framework has been completely replaced. I took inspiration from bullet-hell games and globalized the bullet calculations in the physics server. That makes bullets an unbelievable amount more efficient, especially on low end hardware. I also improved the light calculations, culling and rendering distance. Also the AudioWave system and "eyes" of the NPCs got far FAR more efficient. And now something that took up my last two weeks of free time. Settings! I build the settings framework. The player can control everything from light calculations to render distance to physics system updates and accuracy and so much more. But as soon as I tested the SteamDeck I notices much lower performance compared to most other weak hardware I tested on. After way to much anger and testing I found culprit: Jolt Physics (Extension) Explanation: When I started development Jolt was not part of Godot. So I used and updated the extension version... well that causes EXTREME issues and low hardware starts to cry and scream trying to run it. Switching to Jolt Builtin and then changing a few physics settings and code execution point's and it runs! AHHHHHHHHHHHHH! YES THE AAHHH IS NEEDED! Well what are the numbers? Running the game with its "Base/SteamDeck" Performance Settings runs relatively stable between 60FPS (around 40 when it gets really busy and full). I also tested a PC from 2014 (with comparable performance but over 200 Watt more needed to do so xD) and it runs around 60-70FPS! These numbers are around the same what other modern immersive sim's pull on the same hardware. On my main PC the game runs at around 300+ FPS (Ryzen 9 7900X and RX 7900XT) :D! Now I can FINALLY finish the settings stuff and then finish level 2, polish level 1 and make the trailer! I hope I can get the trailer out around December, maybe a little later! The "maybe later" is because I also want the Itch.io and SteamStore page online at the same time as the trailer goes public and I don't know how long this takes to create that and get int approved. And below is a screenshot from the nearly done settings menu. I disabled the background because it would spoil story stuff early then I want right now and it is not 100% done. The settings also need a little improvements but are far enough to show. I think the only things missing in the settings are to integrated the keybind-change framework into the UI and maybe a few Gameplay settings into into there own tab.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.09.08 - Streets completed, Reworked Audio effects</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=31</link>
			<description>After a lot of small things, the streets have been completed. "Quest", Dialog's, Ambiances and so much more. I needed to completely re-implement the Audio Effect system (Echo in big rooms or muffled sound in small spaces and so on). That was not that much work (One evening I think was all it took) but now it works FAR more efficient and cleaner. The detection quality is slightly lower but it is just not worth the CPU power for like 1% better room detection. I am currently work on the outposts. On of them is already fully planed out and half implemented. After those are done and the side story's are written and implemented I will continue with the GOV building and then FINALLY with the main FRP building. After that play-testing, fixing Level 1 and then I can make Level 3. I am already very excited! Especially because around the time I am a good amount into Level 3 I will make the Steam Page public and will also release a first real Trailer and not just a Teaser. Nearly 2 years (and on release probably even more) of continuously hard work and near every hour I have free for hobby's coming together.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.08.28 - Work on the streets goes along very well, Complete rework of the Culling system, adding new detection framework and fixing Jolt issues</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=30</link>
			<description>Important stuff first: The work on the streets goes forward extremely great! And in not to much more time level 2 will be finished and is ready for full on play-testing. I am also working in the background on a Trailer. And now some extremely technical stuff for those interested: I noticed the performance near many single objects got lower the expected. There was definitely something wrong. After some debugging I found the cause, StaticBody3Ds. Jolt dose not recommend using detection of them at all and is disabled by default. Now I see why. Then I disabled it and refactored my culling system to work again. I used layer detection up to this point to keep it as broad as possible but this backfired. I used Area3Ds for detection (A mistake if I think about it now, now that I know groups with a simple node can be used with distance calculation in an extra thread. I am still sure from a calculation perspective the Area3D with overlap detection approach should work better but the Physics engine can not handle this many Areas at once). That worked but then Jolt just started not processing many objects... reason: Jolt can only handle a limited amount of Area3Ds... . Then I created a new detection system that can just be plugged-in into Scenes so they just have it after that (That is the "groups" stuff just mentioned). That worked BUT then the SaveSystem got mad at me again because it dose not like the references needed to get from the Culling-Node to the Instanced-Scene-Root or Sub-Roots depending on the Scene. After removing the problem causing part many aspects reset between seasons... that meant painstakingly debugging every issue noticed while playing and building a passer for that type or information having issues... again. The old stuff used methods not compatible with the Culling References. Then I had to fix a few Bugs that were created thanks to all the changes just mentioned. And now I can add the last few things in the streets and I can start on the outposts. After that I can finish the gov-building and finally the cooperation building('s). A cool side-effect of the new-new culling system is it puts a little more usage onto the CPU, but that seems to be more efficient from a main thread perspective so GPU can now run way faster thanks to that. The FPS improvements are conditional (not all places in the Levels had the issues with StaticBody3Ds) but when it helps it helps a good amount. Very happy about that. To say that the last 5 days were technical and very intensive thinking hours is an understatement. The last time this project needed this much concentration from me, was while creating the Bone Systems of the Player and NPC models.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.08.21 - "Enclosed" Level 2, Fixed many Bugs, added Roof areas and added more Story</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=29</link>
			<description>I know. This DevLog is all over the place and very unfocused but to keep it short: I decided to work on the streets between all the other main places. And in Long: Last time I wrote I am unsure if I want to continue with the gov-building or the streets, and at the end I just started on the streets. Currently I think I am halfway done with the streets already. The main things are all the interactions in-between main places, NPC's and small events. After that is fully finished I will add the outposts that can be done optionally. They will definitely tie into the main story but can be overseen/get unnoticed (Similar to all the countless side events happening in DeusEX or Peripeteia). Just the closing of all Level "Holes and open sides" made the level feel so much more like a lived in place and something in a game (no matter how strange that sounds). While recording footage or game-testing a found my self multiple times already just playing the game or getting into "Immersive sim" mindset of "I wonder what happens when I do X and Y" and then the interaction just work. I have a very good feeling about the game and the upcoming year and a possible release sooner rater then latter. I am still unsure if I am gonna release a Demo or just work on it a little longer and go full release directly. Demo is definitely great for the players to see what is coming but the time and work I would ratter put into the full game, especially because it is already so far in development compared to other Immersive sims that had a demo far earlier in Development compared to my current development state. I also don't have any pressure or external finical support which gives me the opportunity to just do what I want. But I definitely got some eyes on the project by now and I want to make sure to use the opportunity to get as much eyes on my game as possible. After nearly two years of working on RE//POSSESSED I can see the goal approaching but also notice how much I overshot the initial goal. Level 2, aka. "The City", especially is so much MUCH bigger then all other Levels and Areas in game and really is a challenge to overcome (Thankfully the worst and biggest obstacles are already behind me). Level 3, 4 and 5 gonna be smaller in scope (Still big and open, but not a hole city lol). I can not wait to get the game over the finish-line and leave my mark on the Immersive Sim landscape and hopefully give the Immersive Sim fan a unique and fun approach to their favorite genre.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.08.10 - Church done</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=28</link>
			<description>The church is now fully done. I added all models, dialog's, triggers, events and ambiance and music. I really love the fights and dialog's that can be had here. The performance improvements also keep on coming. I decided it is worth to add "Occlusion culling" to the project. Nothing more then enabling the project setting and then fixing like 3 models that had it on by default by accident. Now a can add "OccluderInstance3D" and assign them a polygons to fit my needs. Most models are not compatible with the automatic "Occlusion" because the Meshes are often layers deep in the Scenes. It would also be unwanted because it would cause issues with rendering. I placed the "Occluder's" in places where the player goes inside or the view is obscured by walls. It was really not that much work to place the "Occlusion" That brings a nice amount of stability to the FPS. Not really needed that much anymore but every little but counts at the end. The church is definitely one of my favorite places in Level 2. I put way to much stuff in there and story just goes even more of the rails from here. What part of the city I work next on, I will figure out right after I post this. But now the important part again, pictures!</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.07.22 - Church nearly done. Gigantic Performance improvements</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=27</link>
			<description>The church is nearly done. Only one Room and the Basement room is missing. Then I can add the last 3 or so dialog's, 3 more character specific models, 2 songs and then document it all in my doc. After that the church is done and either the streets or the gov. building is next. An other thing a discovered thanks to brainstorming with my husband was a performance issue thanks to overdraw of all things. I use Blockbench for the models and the exports from it has a more or less "default" material applied by it to conform to gltf standards I guess. The issue is it disables "Culling" or to be more precise it  enables "DoubleSided". This caused a good amount of performance to get wasted. After discovering it, reading the documentation standard for gltf and checking the files I wrote a script to manually "patch" it into the models on export. Surprisingly only the most used models needed fixed (Buildings and ground-types). The rest is more or less good as is. The performance bump? About 70fps depending on hardware. My GPU is a monster so I did not notice it as much but that is a lot! I always was confused why the models were visible inside-out but now I have an explanation. The only bigger issue coming from that is that Level 1 now really needs cleanup. It was build before I had figured out how to efficiently structure scenes for my game. It was more or less used to figure this out in the first place. Now, thanks to this, the environment is, compared to Level 2, really inefficient. It needs to have its BaseMesh and Navigation mesh spitted and cleaned-up for OneSide Rendering. It is not too much work, just annoying. I will start with that as soon as Level 2 is finished and then use the experience from that to build Level 3. Level 2 is really my favorite part of my game and it's world. So beautiful, I nailed down my art-style so much and now really know how to do things to get what I want and then actually liking it. It is so much work but so worth it!</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.07.07 - Translation Framework fully integrated</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=26</link>
			<description>Just a small update on that front. From the start I tried to use as much Game language independency as possible so translating will be extremely easy later. I still used static names and texts on items and the UI up until now. But I finally seat down and integrated the rest of the translation framework and moved everything over to the translation files. Now it should be extremely easy adding new languages. The settings for the main menu are usually made to the end of the game development because only then is known what exists and what is possible/needed. So I bound the translation function to a button for now. The plans for now are to release the game in English. Later more languages are possible but there would be native speakers that also speak English needed to translate the full game and it also depends on how worth it is to translate it.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.07.06 - A lot of small things done</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=25</link>
			<description>I started working on the church and realized, because of its size and scale I need many assets around it too (It dose take up some parts of the streets) and so I needed a few more assets and Modules to be done next. Then I realized I need many of the same Modules in the starting area of Level 2. So I changed plans and starting developing the Modules, extended the Dialog script-parser and fixed a few bugs. Then I polished a few WIP.-Modules and now I will finish populating the starting area and then move on to the church area finally. I think currently the only thing missing in the start area is Neon Signs. The rest has been done already. And then I can create the outside of the church, then move on to creating a few models for the inside, write the dialog and triggers and then script the events. Music is definitely needed here to, maybe a theme for wandering the streets must be created earlier then expected too. I will see when it comes to it. That's about it for the current work. The stuff coming next is still open. I could either start filling the streets, or work one one of 3 outposts, the gov-building or even the ending area. Only after finishing all of that, full play-testing can start and polishing Level 2 can be completed. One thing is for sure, this is one of the biggest Levels I ever worked on. Even thought there were some downtime in between and I worked on different stuff in the game from time to time, the amount of research, IRL. exploring and then planing for Level 2 is unbelievable for me. I am a little happy that later Levels will be a little more abstract and need less research and ground up development to be honest. But I definitely will be the most proud about the amount of work in Level 2.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.06.22 - Warehouse fully completed</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=24</link>
			<description>The warehouse has been fully completed. Some more testing, fixes and the music has been completed to be more precise. Now it is time for the church Area.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.06.19 - Warehouse dialog's, play-testing and fixes completed and small Updated about the progress</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=23</link>
			<description>There was still a little bit to fix and play-test after completing it. I also fixed many bugs, added 5 new features to the framework, adjust the dialogs and trigger and updateded the lore and story documentation to make writing/the story fleshing out process easier. I still need one song for the warehouse. It must be the stealth and fight theme at the same time there. I will probably do it off and on over time or in one go. I never know with that music stuff, it's hard, still no updates in the maybe/maybe-not searching process for a musician for the OST. The next area to be worked on will be the church. The amount of assets needed there is manageable but gameplay mechanics, an imposing environment and interconnected story strings will be the bread and butter of this area. How far is the development? Hard to say but level 2, I would say, is 40% done. The % and amount of work is not that connected because many assets are for multiple areas. 3 main areas, stuff in between those, 4 smaller areas and a small things here and there are still missing. Is this amount of work for all levels needed? No, the city level is a thing I always wanted in the game and citys are just way to big LOL. But other levels like level 3 and 5 are far more streamlined and easier to implement. Dont get me wrong, the levels will still be big, but need far less then a city that is full with people.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.06.10 - Warehouse Assets, placement and quests completed</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=22</link>
			<description>The warehouse is done. It needs a little play-testing still, one song and I must make sure the triggers work but it is now 100% playable. It is only one part of the big city and marks an other milestone with RE//POSSESSED because so, and I mean it, SO much stuff has been created used and needed all over Level 2. One of my favorites is the walkway and especially the SN433. Like any overpowered Sniper is it a lot of fun getting the enemy's out of the blue.</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.05.29 - Restaurant has been completed and the base of the warehouse is done</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=21</link>
			<description>I wrote it on my blog already but I had many technical issues in my household that started around 2025.04.19 or so. My PC needed maintenance, then the PC of my husband started acting up and as if that is not enough he switched to Linux and I needed my help getting it setup and running and we also changed a few things in our living space. Sooo... yeah a lot of little things took up a lot of time. I still found time to continue working on the game but not as much as usual. Since last week my free time is free enough again to work on the game as much as before April. I finished the restaurant already a while ago and the warehouse is in work for around a month now. I already got all he basics done. Meaning models, placement, layout and so on. The only things missing now are lighting, NPC positions, dialog's, a few textures, one song and event-trigger. After this I either start working on one of the three outposts/world NPC's (they need relatively little work) or the church. As soon as the lighting and NPC's are done I will post images to show what has been in the kitchen.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.04.13 - Bar fully done</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=20</link>
			<description>Bar again? Yes I decided to do the music on its own and not parallel. It is really exhausting for me and I still need to learn a lot about it and that takes more time then anyone would think. I also fixed a few bugs, added a few features to improve the ambiance sound a good bit. And now I am working on Restaurant in the starting area. It only needs a few dialog's, NPC's and pathfinding checks/adjustments, aka. not that much left to do there, and then I will continue with the warehouse. I am very exited to do that because it will be a big building with multiple separate patrols, mechanics and "Quests" that intersect there.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.04.05 - Bar area finished!</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=19</link>
			<description>The bar are has been finished. Only... well the music is still missing but I will make the music in parallel while making the next area. Music takes me a lot of time and I can only do so much per day before my brain loses the energy for making it. Music is hard LOL. Most often I make some music/continue working on a song and the when I feel exhaust from it switch do level building or Lore/Dialog/Script writing. I really REALLY love how the Bar came out. And it is a HUGE progress for Level2 and assets in general. So SO many new assets needed all over the map are now done. The progress gets faster and faster for new areas because the assets most commonly needed are already there. I will also from now on add less and less detail what or where the area's are. Just so the players following the development closer still can get surprised. The amount of stuff I show stays the same, but less spoilers will be Included so to say. The game comes along absolutely GREAT!</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.03.23 - Level 2 - Integrated all Models into the Level and removed "BlockOut" completely</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=18</link>
			<description>It was a lot of work but the full environment is done and can now be filled with some interiors, decorations, where needed, and the planed NPC's and there "Missions/Paths/Quests/What ever the name is for how I am doing that stuff" can be integrated. And now the important part. TEASER IMAGES. NOT FINAL AND NOT DONE:</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.03.13 - Small fix to the RSS-Feed</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=17</link>
			<description>Just a small fix. The RSS-Feed of the Dev-Logs were not formatted correctly. Now the RSS-Feed should work well again.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.03.10 - Updated to Godot 4.4 and Jolt 15.0, cleaned Project structure, planed story and NPC's and finished all main City models</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=16</link>
			<description>The last 2 to 3 weeks I had not as much time as I would have liked too (I was sick lol), but in the free hours I had I still managed to finish quite a few things. I finished all Models that are needed to now fully build the City level aka. Level 2 and replace all placeholders. The interiors will be build in engine with "Interiors Building blocks". They are also already planed out and only need to be placed. The Update to the new Godot and Jolt version was done today and was relatively easy. As usual a few things broke. One overside mine that never was a problem because of a Godot bug now manifested and needed to be fixed. That was easy, just a few Collider issues. Then a few Settings changes and ports to new implementations in Godot and that was it with code changes. A few settings in Jolt needed to be changed but after that it ran fine too. The new improvements showed instantly with the way shades are now faster to execute and THANK GOD Shader compilation is no longer a issue. Just a one time thing and done. Most of the work were the models at the end and I'm very happy they finally are done. A few special Models like Main Story NPC's or a few special assets like Interior parts of special Buildings will be created as needed. They don't take up much time and its easier to make them when everything around them is already prepared. I want to make sure that my ideas around them are fully planed out before creating them to avoid doing it multiple times and make them fit there environment. And also: It's a nice change of pace to create special assets from time to time. The Story and the places are around 90% done planing out. Currently I will need at least 5 new songs for Level 2, 1 for Level 1 and a lot of Dialog Text I'm already very eager to write. Creating dialog for the story is a lot of work but SO FUN. Making music is not my strength sadly xD but I will try my best. I would actually like to look into working with a musician that actually knows how to make good music but that would blow the roof of the budget for the game. This is a passion project after all and I already invested not a minuscule amount of money into it.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.03.01 - Level 2 Concept executed and "Blocking Out" done</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=15</link>
			<description>The concept for level 2 is now fully laid out and the full level has been "Blocked out". For those who do not know what that means: The collision, placement of models and paths are done/reserved and only need to be replaced with the "final" actual model and not just a colored block. Now I need to finish the building models and integrate the NPC's and interiors of the open buildings. Maybe flesh out the underground area some more too. From concept to actually playable is so slow to develop for, but as soon as the Level Environment is inside the Level-Scene everything goes really fast (and then slow again because of the final 90% rule xD). I'm just happy the slow part is finally over and the fun part of actual lore integration can start. Currently everything is going as planed and is inside the predicted time frame.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.02.16 - Leaving Pre-Alpha, entering Alpha. Level-Load/Menus/Save/Load/File-Pipline done and way to many fixes.</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=14</link>
			<description>FINALLY! I am happy to announce that RE//POSSESSED has left the Pre-Alpha stage! All features are implemented and "working". Now in the Alpha stage the playtesting will wramp up a lot and the primary focus lays now on lore, Level designing/building and getting the assets looking as intended (Like menus for example.). Besides that Bugs will be fixed that come up while level building or ticketed by the playtesters. I'm really happy to have come this far! The last goal in development was Save/Load and Level-Load and then it all escalated to the full completion of the menu system, the complete pipeline for loading levels and saves and crushing all bugs in the way of the Alpha stage. Scope what is that (Classic immersive sim dev mindset xD)? This resulted in the leaving of the Pre-Alpha stage. All levels currently shipped with the internal playtest-build can be completed and played as currently intended (they a still buggy probably as you can imagine for a alpha, duh.). A other great unrelated event is the EA release of Peripeteia! We all know what this means: A few days of maximum degeneracy and playing Peripeteia any free minute someone has! My greatest congratulations to the developers!</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.02.12 - Save/Load System completely done and Level transition code also finished implementing</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=13</link>
			<description>Finally, FINALLY it is done. Including the UI, integration with the UI and UX, binding's and so on. The level switch code is also done and now only needs the signals connected and testing and maybe a level done screen or something so it is not just press here and next level. The Menu design is not final and only a framework so I can easily improve it with changing numbers later. Now it is Level 2 time and bug fixing for a few thing that came up with testing.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.02.03 - Save/Load System nearly done</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=12</link>
			<description>Nearly everything is working. I got it to behave like I wanted. It literately can be compared to a Save-State in Emulation Software or in Virtual Machines in regard how detailed the amount of information is that gets saved. TL;DR: EVERYTHING. How hard was it? HARD. Like really really HARD. I used the Binary serialization API and the the ResourceSaver and still had to incl. multiple custom ways to save data between running Sessions. Some did Godot just not touch or were reset regardless. Worst were at runtime created Objects and Animation States. Now I only have to fix a few things in the Player and NPC's code that are not set correctly from the start after loading a Save, then the Save/Load Framework is completed. After that the Level-Transition must be tested and integrated into the Save/Load framework too. The code is already done it only must be integrated incl. a Level Exit and Entry Node. That will be very easy. Just must be done cleanly so it must not be touched again. Building the Save-framework was very annoying and harder then it should be in a game engine but it is nearly done and I can hopefully leaf it alone after this. It is very generic and should work with all nodes build in the future and should only need a few flags in the Scene to be working immediately.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.01.24 - It's Save/Load and Level transition time</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=11</link>
			<description>I have finally fixed and/or finished all systems and Backlog things in the way to be able to start testing/implementing the Save/Load system's. I'm really hoping this is gone be not to annoying or I'm in for a ride... . We will see. As soon as I have it working I will definitely post about it. This is not gonna be a easy checkpoint system as many games have. This will fully save the state of a level like in other immersive sim games like Deus Ex, Peripeteia, Prey (2017), also sometimes referred to as "Typhon", and so on. I really love these save system that let the player do what ever they want and try It as often as they want without wasting time, meaning very quick load times are important. I will try to keep file size, load and save times as low as possible and also, if possible, will also incorporate multithreading to keep the process from hanging.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.01.20 - Fixed all backlog bugs and added needed features</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=10</link>
			<description>Fixed all bugs in the backlog that were still in the way of testing/implementing Save/Load. Added one gameplay-feature from the backlog. Now only one other feature needs to be completed to be able to test/implement Save/Load fully into the framework. With Save/Load also comes the Level-Switch and Data-Transfer code. Meaning the full Save/Load  implementation will probably take up some time (or maybe the concept implementation works from the start and it is easier then expected... probably not XD). Culling system works perfect so far from testing. Also did some balancing fixes with the enemy's and NPC's in the finished level.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.01.18 - Extended culling system, added Multithreading and fixed bugs</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=9</link>
			<description>The culling system from the last update had some issues. If you move an Area3D in Godot the Area3D Triggers "body_exited" and "body_entered" A LOT. It is either by design because areas are designed to be moved continuously like this or it is probably just a bug. The fix was to make a custom old detection and new detection method and compare. I also added a separate layer for better performance when detecting and added multithreading for good measure. The performance improvements are now more then I expected. Multithreading makes games run better on low end modern hardware but makes it harder for older low end hardware because of the increased CPU architectural needs. But to simulate may things at the same time and put culling on the top of that, there is now way around it. After that I fixed the last bugs in the current backlog. Only one feature and 3 Bugs are now missing to start testing the Save/Load system.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.01.15 - Performance BOOST and fixes</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=8</link>
			<description>As planed I started fixing bugs, got a few out of the way and then found a bit of a performance issue with the size of a few levels and the amount of enemy's. They decide many things on the fly and that takes a good amount of performance, especially when the player or items are involved. The build-in culling and LOD systems of Godot were not enough. I also use many (often dynamic) light source that also needs a good amount of performance. I plan to offer a pre-backed lights option at some point that will help weaker hardware. Godot makes it hard to get Level Nodes without iterating into other scenes by accident. This made it a little bit of a bigger task to figure out a way to get around that and disable nodes dynamically. I build a system that can disable nodes or parts of them I deem performance intensive and enable them if the player comes into the area. It is fully dynamic, not trigger or area bound but player bound and should work great with the large levels. Below is an example with the setting turned up to max to make it better visible.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.01.12 - More cleanup and finishing Level structure</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=7</link>
			<description>Fixing a few Bugs in the back log and added last Level details, the last few enemy's got placed, moved or equipped and the last few structure's in the ending area of the first level got placed. Now I have one fully finished and implemented/build level from beginning to end. Next are a few bugs with player node to fix and then the save/load system debugging/implementing/fixing can begin. After that, level 2 is on the list to be completed, tested and cleaned up.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2025.01.08 - Fixing Bugs and cleaning up</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=6</link>
			<description>After my well deserved two weeks of Christmas vacation it's time to get back to gamedev. As expected, the game-testing and gameplay testing rounds showed a few bugs until right before release (and even after when just playing). That was what has been mostly been fixed today. I added more Crossair features and cleanups, tightened up the level design here and there and fixed the last few bugs on the list from the trailer production.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2024.12.31 - Rename from ProjectCWC to RE//POSSESSED</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=5</link>
			<description>After some feedback from the lovely developers of Peripeteia, I decided to change the name and settled on one of my favorite from the possible candidates: RE//POSSESSED or REPOSSESSED. It fits with the theme and lore of the game world and has no direct connection to anything.</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2024.12.24 - REPOSSESSED is now officially revealed!</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=4</link>
			<description>I will from now on updated this log about everything involving the game, to some extend do some promotion and keep building the Levels and extend the story and world building. How frequent I will update this log or the promotional pages and account's depends on the current workload and time I have. I will continue working as much if not even more on the game as the last year and a half. And now the important part: Head over to the main page and have a look at the gameplay trailer.</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2024.11.11 - Preparing to publicly announce REPOSSESSED</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=3</link>
			<description>All the development until now were mostly private. Sometime I did mentioned in posts what is happening in the background on my blog. I also released a few teaser images in my media library. Now the game has everything what is needed to actually play the game. The last two or so months and most of the development from now on is nearly fully consumed by level design, NPC creation, world building, music creation, bug fixing and fleshing out the story.</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2024.08.13 - Framework complete</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=2</link>
			<description>Around that time I was done with the framework of the game. Many library's, systems and interactions needed to build the modules for the game are feature complete. Most of the modules usually needed for in-game interactions and gameplayevents were also nearly done. The custom Dialog system, custom audio system, and custom inventory system is finished and mainly needs the Assets now. Much of the current development time (the last (and next) 2 or 3 weeks) were focused on the audio Assets (meaning SFX, Music and ambiance. Thanks to a good friend for helping me getting all the sounds and ambiance track's) and world building / NPC' and there needs. Items and custom scripts that slot into the framework are build on the way. The framework should allows for fast development on that front thanks to all the exposed API's in the interaction's framework</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2024.01.10 - Full commitment</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=1</link>
			<description>At this point I already hat a very very basic play environment with many mechanics implemented. Thankfully my husband convinced me, while we were on a date, to commit fully to the the development of dream game project from now on. I tried myself on different versions of the game in the past already but stooped development after a few days at the most. The idea of REPOSSESSED was existing for a long time already an vent through many different types of games, from with a 2D platformer, going to a 3D 'jump and run', "text adventure" inside a IDE, and so many more. My love for Immersive sim grew a lot over the years and then one and one came to getter and now we have REPOSSESSED.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RE//POSSESSED - 2023.10.07 - Started Model and Framework building</title>
			<link>https://REPOSSESSED.catwithcode.moe/Dev_Log/Dev_Log.html?item=0</link>
			<description>The game devolvement did not start at this point yet. I just toyed around with Godot and tried my hand on 3D model creation, music creation and texturing. Here a few models I was building to get familiar with the tools. Non of these models are in the game. I will not put the music from back then here. It did just not sound good. I also tested multiple joint types for arms, legs and body movement. The pre-final joint design can be seen in the last image. The final type I use is far simpler and works better.</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
    </channel>
</rss>
